To Whom It May Concern.

My Name is Anthony J. Manenti -

I am a Graduate of UNC – Greensboro's College of Arts and Sciences. I am also a graduate of The Coding Bootcamp at UNC Chapel Hill's Spring 2018 cohort where I was exposed to the MERN stack of technologies used in the creation of web based applications.

I have also completed UNC's Coding Bootcamp. I am a member of the 2018 Spring Cohort. In Bootcamp I was exposed to HTML, CSS, Javascript, MySQL, MongoDB, React and Node. I enjoyed the experience of working with other classmates to create and present two full stack applications. During this time I learned the importance of self analysis and learning to be comfortable with technologies and techniques that would challenge me. I also learned the importance of communicating and sharing ideas.

I have over a decade worth of work experience in Tech. I started from humble beginnings as a computer repair technician and have worked with managed service providers in the triangle area. My work has always pushed me, and has been humbling. There is always something new to learn.

I feel that I have the potential to be a valuable asset to any creative team, given the right structure and balance. I have a continued interest in the field and work constantly, even outside of the bootcamp to develop my skills and widen my breadth of experience.

Yours truly,

Anthony J. Manenti
Applicant

https://github.com/imaginethat01

ANTHONY J. MANENTI

Professional Resume:

Education:

• The Coding Bootcamp at The University of North Carolina

Intensive course in Full Stack Development

Fluency in MERN Stack and the development of dynamic applications using front and back-end technologies and database query languages. Project Management experience including two full stack applications.

• University of North Carolina - Greensboro

Bachelors of Arts and Sciences

Concentration: English Literature. Publishing. Design.

Work History:

• Imagine That Solutions

2013 - 2018 Primary Account Representive

Responsible for the creation and maintenance of eCommerce solutions and the management of analytics powered advertising tools

• The Computer Cellar Durham

2017-2018 Repair Technician

Polished the craft of laptop and small device repair. Successfully navigated difficult problems relating to common consumer hardware ans software.

• The ITGuys

2017-2018 Technical Specialist

Responsible as an MSP to a list of clients. And assistant in the installation of business and enterprise class networking assets.

• Intrex Computers INC / Microbarn.com

2013-2015 Lab Technician, Warehousing Agent.

Learned the fundamentals of diagnostics and computer repair, accounting and how to manage large sets of inventory.

PERSONAL REFERENCES



List of Relevant Contacts:

Current Employer (Computer Cellar Durham)

Daryn O'Shea (Owner) 919-824-3035

Gabriel Caviness (Supervisor) 919-949-1392

Simon Beery (Co-Worker) 919-370-6929

Educational Training (Coding Bootcamp UNC- Chapel Hil)

Will Pike (Instructor) 949-527-0499 pike.wil@gmail.com

Maria Wong (Teachers Assistant)
mwong770@gmail.com

Ariel Borochov (Teachers Assistant) ariel.borochov@aol.com

Tim Tucker (Classmate) 615-956-5179

Personal Mentor (RedHat Support)

William Clarke 919-597-1046